Guide to the Office of Alumni Affairs Homecoming and Reunion Records, 1974-2021 UA 208
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Office of Alumni Affairs Homecoming and Reunion Records
1974-2021
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Office of Alumni Affairs, Rice University
UA 208
0.5 Linear Feet 1 box
This collection contains Homecoming and Reunions publications and ephemera from the Office of Alumni Affairs from 1974-2021.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Alumni Affairs, in association with the Association of Rice Alumni, maintains communication with Rice alumni, encouraging them to stay connected with the University intellectually and socially and to assist in maintaining the welfare of the University. The annual Homecoming and Reunion events are coordinated by a Committee Chairperson, serving on the Association of Rice Alumni Board. The Homecoming and Reunions committee provides events for alumni to connect with each other, oversees volunteers and speakers, and tracks participation levels.
Scope and Contents
The Office of Alumni Affairs, in association with the Association of Rice Alumni, maintains communication with Rice alumni, encouraging them to stay connected with the University intellectually and socially and to assist in maintaining the welfare of the University. The annual Homecoming and Reunion events are coordinated by a Committee Chairperson, serving on the Association of Rice Alumni Board. The Homecoming and Reunions committee provides events for alumni to connect with each other, oversees volunteers and speakers, and tracks participation levels.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was transferred by The Office of Alumni Affairs, 2010. 2021 donation by Helen Toombs.
Related Materials
See Information and Photograph files for Homecoming at Woodson Research Center. See also Rice University Alumni Affairs / University Events records, UA 386, Woodson Research Center, Fondren Library, Rice University.
Index Terms
Subjects
Reunions; Universities and colleges
Document Types
reports; programs (documents); newsletters; invitations; letters (correspondence); corrrespondence
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University
- Series I. Homecoming and Reunions publications and ephemera, 110952
  - 1974, 110953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1981, 110954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1982, 110955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1983, 110956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1984, 110957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1985, 110958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1986, 110959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1987, 110960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1988, 110961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1989, 110962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1990, 110963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1991, 110964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2021 (Box 1, Folder 13)